# **OLGA CURYLO**

# **Full-Stack Developer**

curylo.olga@gmail.com

07452950476

London

Github

in. LinkedIn

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Together - web app

Developer, Designer, Frontend, Backend Click to see live app

April 2023 - July 2023

**Typescript**, **Python, Sanic**, Mayim, HTML, CSS, Figma, **SQLite**, esbuild, NGINX, Pipenv,

#### TailwindCSS, React, React Router

- Currently developing a full-stack app that lets you swipe movies you want to watch and generate lists of movies to watch together with your friends.
- Backend written in Python 3.10 using Sanic
  Framework, Mayim used for SQLite database
- Frontend in React and Typescript
- Used esbuild for frontend setup
- Basic NGINX configuration

# **Breazy** - breathing exercises web app

Developer, Frontend Click to see live app

January 2022 - December 2022

React, React Hooks, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Framer Motion, React Transition Group, Jest, React Testing Library

• Built a responsive, accessible web app in

#### **ABOUT ME**

After 5 years working as a manager in clubs in Cracow, I decided to use my time as a stay-at-home mum as an opportunity to change my career path and become a software engineer. I dedicated my time to developing two working products. I learned many modern technologies and expanded my knowledge. I love to learn and programming gives me lots of fun. Harvard's CS50 made me a much better and faster developer. I enjoyed my time as a single developer and now I would like to solve real business problems, become part of a team, and code on a bigger scale.

## **EDUCATION**

Harvard University's CS50,

Eloquent Javascript,

React with a mobile-first approach

- Collaborated using Trello with a friend learning UX and design
- Deployed at Github Pages
- Tested using Jest and React Transition Group

# **Dulwich Hamlet FC** - fanpage

Developer, Designer, Frontend

Click to see live page

may 2022 - current

Next.js, React Hooks, Typescript, HTML, CSS,

Figma, Inkscape, Twitter Api

- Originally written in Next 12, using CSS Modules and Twitter API to show the club's timeline.
- Later rewritten using React with Typescript,
  Vite, and Tailwind CSS
- Unfortunately, I encountered problems with the Twitter API, and the project has become more of a landing page.

### MOST RECENT WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Tak Bylo**

Manager 2014 - 2015

Cracow, Poland

- Worked as a manager in a newly opened club-cafe
- Organised music and cultural events
- Managed a team of 10 people

Advent of Code, CodeWars, freeCodeCamp, Udemy

#### **SKILLS**

**VSCode** 

Accessibility, C, CSS, Figma, Flask, Framer Motion, Git, GitHub, HTML5, Inkscape, ' Javascript, Jest, Linux, Next.js, Node.js, Pandas, Pydantic, Python 3, React, React Hooks, React Router. Sanic, SQL, SQLite, TailwindCSS, React Testing Library, Trello, Typescript,